[{"answer": "Yes, the official -- the ball sits at the 40 yard line.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "And, Mark, it appears to me that the players are slowly starting to trickle back on the field, is that your assessment as you're looking?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Oh, I love the man, I voted for him originally.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Do you like what you see for maybe the second term Obama already?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, it is.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "America needs to find other business models, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Don, I can barely hear you, my man.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Joe Carter?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "We've got a school shooting.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "Ma'am?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Chardon High School.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What school?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Yes, ma'am.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "UNIDENTIFIED 911 OPERATOR: Chardon High School?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "What I -- what I really -- what was going through my mind was I had to get out of the high school and really nothing else flows through your mind.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 282, "question": "The moment that you were shot what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 281}, {"answer": "I had a lot of support.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "How did you deal with it?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I mean, I did, yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Did you despair?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "Well, I had a lot of support from other people texting me and calling me that are in wheelchairs.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Or what was it that they did that helped you?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "What was that like for you as his mother?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "They said that they were cautiously optimistic when they came out of surgery, but -- so we're still hoping and praying.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "What is the prognosis they made?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well, if somebody who's been through it but has an outlook that's positive.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Very particular support group that knows exactly what you've been through?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I would love that.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Shake on it?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Does that bring it all back?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, obviously, I had to -- I had to switch around my career a little bit that I was aiming for.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "But aside from that, have you set yourself things that you really want to achieve?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "I wanted to be just an electrician in the union and I don't believe that can happen practically right now.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What would you want to be?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I was doing a lot of current therapies, you know, psychiatry, psychology, which I started in 2011.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Before you met Tony, what was -- what was your life like?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "Did it help, any of that?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Basically insomnia.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "So you had -- why don't you tell him what your symptoms were at the time?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "The rock bottom moment for me in a sense was -- it was after my second divorce, just being -- I pushed so many people away, couldn't figure out why I felt this way.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What was the rock bottom moment for you?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "Well, it's interesting, and we've done this with hundreds of wounded warriors and different soldiers.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "What do you say in this situation?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Well, basically, he has to take back his life.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "What advice would you give him?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Methamphetamine, right.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "He built a small business to start with and one of those young women that worked for him was addicted to meth, is that right?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Why don't you share with him the story of how you end up in your new business?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "What was that like for you?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "I think ferocity of spirit is critical for everybody, but we all have it.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 580, "question": "Or do you have a little bit of (INAUDIBLE), which is that ferocity of spirit?", "qSentId": 579}, {"answer": "Yes, we do.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "ORGAN: Do we all have it?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Most of it -- I think what's really beautiful about most human beings is that we'll do more for others we love than we'll ever do for ourselves.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 625, "question": "Is that a good focus to look at children, to look at other things and say, \"You know what, stop feeling sorry for myself; it's for him, for her, it's for that\"?", "qSentId": 624}, {"answer": "I got to tell you, Tony is absolutely right.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "And Mike, what do you -- what do you say to these people suffering in America right now?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "But actually all those emotions are just barriers to getting back on your feet, aren't they?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Certainly I think without health, you're not around to do anything.", "docId": "130203pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "If I should (INAUDIBLE), you can have any one thing, you can have good health, you can have money, you can have the fame that allows you to inspire people, what would you choose as the one thing?", "qSentId": 721}]